It just felt like he felt a bit guilty as well
德米纳尔好像还有些愧疚
for the fans that came out and watched,
对那些来到现场观赛的球迷
but nothing that could be done.
但也实在无能为力
从22岁到39岁
7座奖杯 连接着17年的北京记忆
首战6比3 7比5 击败哈内斯库
5场比赛后
德约第一次捧起中网奖杯
That'll do it.
比赛结束！
Novak Djokovic reigns supreme in Beijing.
德约科维奇在北京登顶
It's his third title of the season,
这是他的赛季第三冠
the 14th of his young career.
也是他年轻生涯的第十四冠
His third title this year,
他的年度第三冠
the 14th of his stellar career,
也是精彩生涯的第十四冠
and a nice sum of US$500,000 to go with it.
同时收获五十万美元奖金
费什在第二轮赛前退赛 不计胜场
这一届4场胜利 总账来到九胜
Back-to-back championship runs in 2009-2010.
二零零九 二零一零 连续两届夺冠
Novak Djokovic, your champion, as he defeats David Ferrer,
德约科维奇击败费雷尔 成为冠军
straight sets, 6-2, 6-4, at the China Open.
在中网直落两盘 六比二 六比四
He knows what it's like to hold the trophy aloft.
他很熟悉举起奖杯的感觉
He did so last year.
去年 他就曾这样捧杯
第三次参赛 第三次夺冠
中网14场 全部获胜
It's done.
比赛结束！
And he has done it again,
他再次做到了
for the 14th time in as many matches.
十四场比赛 十四次获胜
Novak Djokovic prevails,
德约科维奇赢下比赛
and he is a three-time champion at the China Open.
第三次成为中网冠军
You heard him say xie xie,
你听到他说“谢谢”
which is thank you in Mandarin.
用的是普通话
That again just going to make it more endearing
这也会更讨人喜欢
to the Chinese fans here.
对这里的中国球迷来说
Djokovic defends his title.
德约科维奇成功卫冕
It's a record fourth trophy in Beijing for Novak Djokovic.
他在北京拿到创纪录的第四座奖杯
He's still unbeaten at this tournament.
他在这项赛事依然保持不败
Nineteen successive victories.
连续十九场获胜
And it was a well-earned victory this afternoon against Rafael Nadal.
今天他战胜纳达尔 赢得实至名归
The Serbian was the better man.
这位塞尔维亚人表现更胜一筹
And now the celebrations can begin in earnest.
现在可以尽情庆祝了
Djokovic is the king in Beijing.
德约科维奇是北京之王
He wins 6-3, 6-4.
他以六比三 六比四获胜
决赛对面是纳达尔
6比3 6比4
德约拿到第四杯
6比0 6比2 击败伯蒂奇
北京的胜场数 来到24
Djokovic makes it five in Beijing.
德约第五次在北京夺冠
His unbeaten streak in the Chinese capital goes on.
他在北京的不败纪录仍在延续
The champion in Beijing for 2014,
二零一四年的北京冠军
Novak Djokovic.
德约科维奇
再胜纳达尔
6次参加 6次夺冠 29场不败
It's six of the best in Beijing,
六度在北京夺冠
simply the best, Novak Djokovic.
实至名归的最佳 德约科维奇
Champion here for a sixth time.
他在这里第六次捧杯
Congratulations to Novak Djokovic.
恭喜德约科维奇
Please take a picture with the presenters.
请与颁奖嘉宾合影
Another wonderful performance from him.
他又一次献上精彩表现
这张榜算的是
从赛事首战起 从未输过
缺席年份不打断 只计实际比赛
同一个起点 塞莱斯澳网33胜
纳达尔法网31胜
德约的北京 还在继续
相隔11年 德约再次回到北京
胜场总账 从29重新出发
第二轮对布云朝克特
1/4决赛对兹维列夫
他都是先丢一盘 再赢下比赛
Novak Djokovic keeps his streak alive here in Beijing.
德约延续了在北京的不败纪录
31 and 0 now for Djokovic.
现在 德约三十一胜 零负
At times it didn't look like it was going to happen today.
今天有些时候 真让人捏了一把汗
He's done it again.
他又一次做到了
Novak Djokovic.
德约科维奇
There's something about this place,
这座球场有种特别的力量
and there is something about this man.
这个男人也有特别之处
The unbeaten record here in Beijing continues.
他在北京的不败纪录仍在延续
Breathe it in.
好好感受这一刻
半决赛 梅德韦杰夫击球打中观众
被取消资格
德约进入决赛
Can you believe it?
你能相信吗？
Just a flurry of errors from Medvedev.
梅德韦杰夫突然连续失误
That's a brilliant combination from Djokovic.
德约这套组合打得太漂亮了
Well, can you believe it?
这下真让人难以置信
After the most extraordinary level in this match,
本场双方打出了极高水平
it has ended on a Medvedev default.
比赛因梅德韦杰夫被判失格而结束
Well, no real protest from Daniil Medvedev,
梅德韦杰夫没有真正提出抗议
but it's hard to argue with the decision
但这项裁决实在难以争辩
from Mohamed Lahyani and the ATP supervisor there.
由拉亚尼和现场ATP监督作出
决赛首盘7比6
第二盘德米纳尔保发后 因伤退赛
比赛结束 遗憾也留在场上
Novak Djokovic moves to within a set
德约科维奇距离冠军只差一盘
of a seventh Beijing title.
那将是他的第七座北京冠军
Puts away the forehand, but he's not looking good, is he?
他拿下正手 但看上去不太舒服
I think he might be done here.
我想 他可能坚持不下去了
Big shake of the head from de Minaur.
德米纳尔重重地摇了摇头
You could just tell he wasn't in a good place.
看得出 他的身体状况很不好
Oh, can you believe it?
天啊 你能相信吗？
I mean that is just heartbreaking for de Minaur.
这对德米纳尔实在太令人心碎了
So disappointing for the fans.
球迷们也感到非常遗憾
But it is a seventh Beijing title
不过 这仍是第七座北京冠军
for Novak Djokovic,
属于德约科维奇
who remains unbeaten in the Chinese capital.
他在北京依然保持不败
34 and 0.
三十四胜 零负
This trophy means much more, much more
这座奖杯的意义远远不止于此
than one trophy, one tournament for all of us,
对我们来说 远不止一杯 一站赛事
so very, very happy for that.
所以我非常 非常开心
第一杯到第七杯 走过17年
北京的奖杯故事 还在继续
It just felt like he felt a bit guilty as well
德米纳尔好像还有些愧疚
for the fans that came out and watched,
对那些来到现场观赛的球迷
but nothing that could be done.
但也实在无能为力
7次捧杯
你最难忘德约的哪一年中网？